we're in Austin Texas man it's hot and
I'm hoping to see some real you know
down south racism how the are you
tonight you guys look fan
terrible what this is is two comedians
going Mike to Mike Pat Dean doesn't know
the meaning of the word can't but let's
try this one more time you can't keep
molesting
children C arador what's happen when
you're born with a ton of white
privilege but you use it all to skip the
line of cce's
[Applause]
pizza feelings get hurt sometimes I
don't want to tell you that Martin orbo
is pretentious but when he drinks he
sticks his pinky
out you can say anything you want in a
roast joke as long as it's as funny as
it is mean if someone can put the
thought in to make a great burn at your
expense like they've thought about it
and like that is awesome Jay's Grandma's
Here how can you beat that I mean even
though I think she should have died a
long time ago his ancestor should have
been in with a peanut allergy Chris
cubis is the guy Hogwart sends when
Hagrid decides the neighborhood is too
dangerous weird like they like their
slogan is you smiling scares the
out of it Ashley looks like she
just poisoned her husband they're really
biting they're really mean but overall
they're really funny checked our show
out this July on Comedy Central thank
you everybody
appreciate